[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the chemical symbol for Boron?", "correct_answer": "B", "incorrect_answers": ["Bn", "Br", "Bo"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The following words belong to which Star Wars character: Then our worst fears have been realized. We must move quickly if the Jedi Order is to survive.?", "correct_answer": "Mace Windu", "incorrect_answers": ["Supreme Chancellor", "Anakin Skywalker", "Obi Wan Kenobi"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What type of character is Jet Li playing in the action movie Romeo Must Die from 2000?", "correct_answer": "Ex cop", "incorrect_answers": ["Taxi driver", "Businessman", "Criminal"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these statements is true about the tongue of the giraffe?", "correct_answer": "All of these", "incorrect_answers": ["The animal uses it as a tool to remove insects from its face.", "It is about 18 inches (45 centimeters) long.", "It is tough."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the name of the submarine in the movie Operation Petticoat?", "correct_answer": "Sea Tiger", "incorrect_answers": ["The Barracuda", "Sea Wolf", "The Tiger Shark"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Britney Spears won the 2003 Worst Actress Award for this movie.", "correct_answer": "Crossroads", "incorrect_answers": ["Fahrenheit  9/11", "Hooves of Fire", "Legends of  a Lost heart"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In August 2002, this wireless company announced the availability of roaming in 35 countries.  It was later bought out by Cingular Wireless.", "correct_answer": "ATT Wireless", "incorrect_answers": ["T-mobile", "VoiceStream", "Verizon Wireless"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What kind of therapy is the Tui na, used in traditional Chinese medicine?", "correct_answer": "Massage", "incorrect_answers": ["Sauna", "Music therapy", "Tea therapy"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "John Ford won the 1940 Academy Award for Best Director for the movie adaptation of what Pulitzer Prize-winning novel?", "correct_answer": "The Grapes of Wrath", "incorrect_answers": ["East of Eden", "To Kill a Mocking Bird", "The Great Gatsby"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which film has the following plot?\nLester Burnham is having a midlife crisis and decides to re-evaluate his life, after becoming infatuated with one of his daughters friends.", "correct_answer": "American Beauty", "incorrect_answers": ["Dead Poets Society", "The Virgin Suicides", "Splendor in the Grass"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In 1536 cheese-makers in Veneto, Italy, created the oldest precedent of falsification by trying to make what cheese?", "correct_answer": "Parmesan", "incorrect_answers": ["Brie", "Kashkaval", "Gouda"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who played the lead character of the movie Benny and Joon?", "correct_answer": "Johnny Depp", "incorrect_answers": ["Judd Nelson", "Emilio Estevez", "Charlie Sheen"]}]